Guide to the Komen Foundation, Houston Records
University of Houston Libraries
- 2004, id73984
  - Race, id74302
    - Activity Reports, id74354 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Printing, id74355 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Kids for Cure, id74356 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Activities, id74357 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Agreement, id74358 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Merchandise, id81571 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - T-shirt Correspondence, id81572 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Volunteer Roster, id142595 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Photographs, id142596 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Survivor Salutes, id142597 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Water, id142598 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Articles, id142599 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Press, id142600 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Binder (Pt. 1), id142601 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Binder (Pt. 2), id142602 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Website, id142603 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Banners, id142604 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Event Guide (Pt. 1), id142605 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Event Guide (Pt. 2), id142606 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Information (Pt. 1), id142607 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Information (Pt. 2), id142608 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Information (Pt. 3), id142609 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Committee Information (Pt. 1), id142610 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Committee Information (Pt. 2), id142611 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Binder (Pt. 1), id142612 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Binder (Pt. 2), id142613 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Co-Chair (Pt. 1), id142614 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Co-Chair (Pt. 2), id142615 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Co-Chair 2 (Pt. 1), id142616 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Co-Chair 2 (Pt. 2), id142617 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Poster, id142619 (Ovs box 32, Item 10)
  - Newsletters, id74303
    - Komen Houston, id74360 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Promotional Literature, id74304
    - Affiliate Training Brochure, id74361 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Sponsorship Information, id74362 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Breast Cancer Awareness Information, id74363 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Website Draft, id74364 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Calendar, id142622 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- 2005, id73985
  - Administrative Documents, id142623
    - Board Members, id142625 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Board Meeting Minutes, id142626 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Board Manual, id142627 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, id142628 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Affiliate Training (Pt.1), id142629 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Affiliate Training (Pt.2), id142630 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Race, id74366
    - Race Script, id74373 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Race Sponsor Information, id74374 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Race Presentation, id74375 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Parking Information, id74376 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Volunteer Form, id74377 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Race Brochure, id74378 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Training Program (CD), id74379 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Images and Information (CD), id74380 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Articles, id142633 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Water Stations, id142634 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Survivor Salute Flags, id142635 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Training II, id142636 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Communications, id142637 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Race Committee, id142638 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Information, id142639 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Binder, id142640 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Printing Projects (Pt. 1), id142641 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Printing Projects (Pt. 2), id142642 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Binder (Pt. 1), id142643 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Binder (Pt. 2), id142644 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Binder (Pt. 3), id142645 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Events, id74367
    - Pasta Party, id74383 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Survivor Party, id74384 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Pledge Program, id74385 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Pink Honor Roll, id74386 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Pink Tie Gala, id74387 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Media Press Conference and Luncheon (CD), id74388 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Survivor Pin Report, id142647 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Sponsors, id74368
    - Chevron, id74389 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Kroger, id74390 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Sponsor Hotels, id74391 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Pink Tie Sponsors, id142649 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Printed Publicity, id74369
    - News clippings, id74392 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - News clippings, id74393 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - News clippings, id74394 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- 2006, id73986
  - Administrative Documents, id74397
    - Board Meeting Minutes, id142652 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Board Manual, id142653 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, id142654 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Strategic Plan, id142655 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Financials, id142656 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Media Notebook (Pt. 1), id142658 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Media Notebook (Pt. 2), id142659 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Komen Affiliate Award Document, id142660 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Grants (Pt. 1), id142661 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Grants (Pt. 2), id142662 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Grant Awards Luncheon, id142663 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Grant Luncheon Photographs, id142664 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - History Committee Photographs, id142665 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Staff Photographs, id142666 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Affiliate Policies, id142667 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Scholarship, id142668 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Race, id74398
    - Manual, id142671 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Brochure, id142672 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Script, id142673 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Poster, id142674 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Crisis Communication Plan, id142675 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Various, id142676 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Moving Forward-Enhancements, id142677 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Sponsorship, id142678 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Sponsorship Opportunities, id142679 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Presenting Gold Sponsors, id142680 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Alison Bell-Survivor, id142681 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Large Race Forum, id142682 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Physical Arrangements (Pt. 1), id142683 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Physical Arrangements (Pt. 2), id142684 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Affiliate/Education/Grantee, id142685 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Affiliate Training Manual, id142686 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Pt. 1), id142687 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook (Pt. 2), id142688 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Information, id142689 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Information, id142690 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Newsletters, id74399
    - Komen Houston, id74414 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Promotional Literature, id74401
    - Calendar, id142693 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Sponsorship Material, id142694 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Membership Material, id142695 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Events, id74400
    - Pink Ribbon Reception, id142697 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - UTMB Donor Dinner, id142698 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, id142699 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Flight Plan, id142700 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Various, id142701
    - Various Photographs, id142703 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Brochures, id142704 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - WYSIWYG Active X HTML Editor, id142705 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - CONVIO Basic Training, id142706 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- 2007, id73987
  - Administrative Documents, id142707
    - Board Meeting Minutes, id142709 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Board Meeting Minutes, id142710 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - By-laws, id142711 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Strategic Plan, id142712 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Financial, id142713 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Consent Agenda, id142714 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Sponsor Stewardship Committee, id142715 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Events, id74420
    - Pink Honor Roll, id74424 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Pasta Party, id74425 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - 3rd Annual Breast Health Summit, id74426 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Pink Tie Gala, id74427 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Convio Summit, id74428 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - UTMB Donor Luncheon, id142717 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Pink Ribbon Reception, id142718 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Tennis Invitational, id142719 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Board Retreat, id142720 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Mobile Mammography, id142721 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Unknown Event Photographs, id142722 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Race, id74421
    - Map, id142725 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Committee Roster, id142726 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Poster, id142727 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Scripts, id142728 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Brochures and Pamphlets, id142729 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Information, id142730 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Affiliate Learning and Development, id142731 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Silver-Crystal Sponsors (Pt. 1), id142732 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Silver-Crystal Sponsors (Pt. 2), id142733 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Sponsor Information, id142734 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Posters (3), id142735 (Ovs box 32, Item 11)
  - Informative Material, id74423
    - Medicaid for Breast & Cervical Cancer, id74433 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Brochures & Pamphlets, id74434 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Informative in-house Publications, id74435 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Invitation Cards, id74436 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Promotional Literature, id74422
    - Sponsorship Booklet, id74437 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Membership Forms, id74438 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Articles, id142738 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Newsletter, id142739 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- 2008, id142381
  - Administrative Documents, id142740
    - Bylaws, id142746 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Board Meeting, id142747 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Board of Directors, id142748 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Membership Rosters, id142749 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Membership, id142750 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Financials, id142751 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Grants, id142752 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Capacity Growth Assessment, id142753 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Strategic Plan, id142754 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Media Training, id142755 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Executive Director Welcome Plan, id142756 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - History Committee, id142757 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, id142758 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Events, id142741
    - 4th Annual Breast Health Summit, id142762 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - 11th Annual Table Talk, id142775 (Box 18, Folder 12a)
    - Advisory Council Luncheon, id142763 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Board Retreat, id142764 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Holiday Luncheon, id142765 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - KBR Charitable Foundation Photograph, id142766 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Mobile Mammography Unit, id142767 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Nancy Owens Memorial Foundation Luncheon, id142768 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Pink Honor Roll, id142769 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Pink Ribbon Reception, id142770 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Pink Tie Gala, id142771 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Unbeatable, id142772 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Unknown Event Photographs, id142773 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Various Events, id142774 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - “An Evening of Comradery for the Cure” Poster, id142761 (Ovs box 32, Item 12)
  - Race, id142742
    - Kickoff Luncheon, id142777 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Marketing Proposal, id142778 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Photographs, id142779 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Pledge Program, id142780 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Printed Materials, id142781 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Race Manual, id142782 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Sponsorship, id142783 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Sponsor Information, id142784 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Printed Materials, id142743
    - Articles, id142786 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Hot Pink Flash, id142787 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Breast Cancer Wellness Magazine, id142788 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Houston Business Journal, id142789 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Houston Lifestyles & Homes, February and October, id142790 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Her Voice, id142791 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - ICON Magazine, March, id142792 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Pamphlets, id142793 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Promise, id142794 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - The Rose Review, id142795 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Together, id142796 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Young Breast Cancer Survivor’s Program, id142797 (Box 18, Folder 44)
- 2009, id142382
  - Administrative Documents, id142798
    - Board of Directors Manual, id142804 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Board Meeting, id142805 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Board of Directors, id142806 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Community Profile, id142807 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, id142808 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Financials, id142809 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Governance Committee, id142810 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - History Committee, id142811 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Strategic Plan, id142812 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Events, id142799
    - 5th Annual Breast Health Summit, id142814 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - 8th Annual Nancy Owens Memorial Foundation Luncheon, id142815 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Annual Awards Luncheon, id142816 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Board/Staff retreat, id142817 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Divas & Dames, id142818 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Pink in the Park, id142819 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Pink Pledge Pals, id142820 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Pink Tie Gala, id142821 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Unknown Event Photographs, id142822 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Various Events, id142823 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Race, id142800
    - Information, id142825 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Pledge Program, id142826 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Manual, id142827 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Printed Materials, id142801
    - Articles, id142829 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Conquest, id142830 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Hot Pink Flash, id142831 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Houston Lifestyles & Homes, April, id142832 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Promise, id142833 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - The Rose Review, id142834 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - The Tanglewood Buzz, id142835 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- 2010, id142383
  - Administrative Documents, id142836
    - Advisory Council, id142841 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Board of Directors, id142842 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Board of Directors Manual (Pt. 1), id142843 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Board of Directors Manual (Pt. 2), id142844 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Bylaws, id142845 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Certificate of Formation, id142846 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, id142847 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Financials, id142848 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Governance, id142849 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Events, id142837
    - 6th Annual Breast Health Summit, id142851 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Awards Luncheon, id142852 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Board Retreat, id142853 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Breast Prosthesis Project, id142854 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Pink Honor Roll, id142855 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Pink Pledge Pals, id142856 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Pink Tie Gala, id142857 (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - The Rose Grand Opening, id142858 (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Think Pink Luncheon, id142859 (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - Various Events, id142860 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Race, id142838
    - Correspondence, id142862 (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - Manual, id142863 (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - Parking, id142864 (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - Printed Materials, id142865 (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - Pledge Program, id142866 (Box 19, Folder 50)
    - Program, id142867 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Printed Materials, id142839
    - Articles, id142869 (Box 19, Folder 52)
    - The Rose Review, id142870 (Box 19, Folder 53)
    - Tanglewood/River Oaks Buzz, id142871 (Box 19, Folder 54)
    - Together, id142872 (Box 19, Folder 55)
- 2011, id142384
  - Administrative Documents, id142873
    - Board of Directors, id142878 (Box 19, Folder 56)
    - Bylaws, id142879 (Box 19, Folder 57)
    - Certificate of Formation, id142880 (Box 19, Folder 58)
    - Correspondence, id142881 (Box 19, Folder 59)
    - Governance Committee, id142882 (Box 19, Folder 60)
    - Grantee Orientation, id142883 (Box 19, Folder 61)
    - Grants, id142884 (Box 19, Folder 62)
    - Large Grants: Application Guidelines, Compliance, Rating, id142885 (Box 19, Folder 63)
    - Large Grants: Community Grants/Review Panel, id142886 (Box 19, Folder 64)
    - Small Grants, id142887 (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - Events, id142874
    - 10th Annual Nancy Owens Memorial Foundation Luncheon, id142889 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Impact Awards Luncheon, id142890 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Leadership Conference, id142891 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Pink Honor Roll, id142892 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Pink Pledge Pals, id142893 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Silver Rose Gala, id142894 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Various Events, id142895 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Warriors in Pink, id142896 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Race, id142875
    - Manual, id142900 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Media Training, id142901 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Pledge Program, id142902 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Printed Materials, id142903 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Rock the Race, id142904 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Sponsorship Opportunities, id142905 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Poster, id142899 (Ovs box 32, Item 13)
  - Printed Materials, id142876
    - Articles, id142907 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Informational Material, id142908 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Promise, id142909 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Together, id142910 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- 2012-2013, id142385
  - Administrative Documents, id142911
    - Board of Directors, id142915 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Budget, id142916 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, id142917 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Events, id142912
    - Advisory Council Luncheon, id142919 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - American Cancer Society President’s Reception, id142920 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Holiday Open House, id142921 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Impact Awards Luncheon, id142922 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Race, id142913
    - Sponsorship Opportunities, id142924 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Printed Materials, id142925
    - Articles, id142927 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Think Pink, id142928 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Together, id142929 (Box 20, Folder 29)
- Memorabilia, id142386
  - T-shirts (12), 1993-1999; id142942 (Box 21, Item 1)
  - Hats (2), 1998; id142943 (Box 21, Item 2)
  - Gym Bag, 1992; id142944 (Box 21, Item 3)
  - T-shirts (12), 2000-2003; id142945 (Box 22, Item 1)
  - Bag, 2003; id142946 (Box 22, Item 2)
  - T-shirts (8), 2004; id142947 (Box 23, Item 1)
  - Visor, 2004; id142948 (Box 23, Item 2)
  - Bags (2), 2004; id142949 (Box 23, Item 3)
  - “Drink Pink” Water Bottle, 2004; id142950 (Box 23, Item 4)
  - “Race for the Cure” Medal, 2004; id142951 (Box 23, Item 5)
  - T-shirts (14), 2005; id142952 (Box 24, Item 1)
  - Pillowcases (3), 2005; id142953 (Box 24, Item 2)
  - Visor, 2005; id142954 (Box 24, Item 3)
  - Water Bottle, 2005; id142955 (Box 24, Item 4)
  - Lanyard and pin, 2005; id142956 (Box 24, Item 5)
  - Canvas Bags (2), 2005; id142957 (Box 24, Item 6)
  - T-shirts (9), 2006; id142958 (Box 25, Item 1)
  - Visors (2), 2006; id142959 (Box 25, Item 2)
  - Hat, 2006; id142960 (Box 25, Item 3)
  - Pillowcases (2), 2006; id142961 (Box 25, Item 4)
  - Canvas Bags (2), 2006; id142962 (Box 25, Item 5)
  - Lanyards, pins, name tags, 2006; id142963 (Box 25, Item 6)
  - Canvas Bags (3), 2007; id142964 (Box 26, Item 1)
  - Pillowcase, 2007; id142965 (Box 26, Item 2)
  - T-Shirts (10), 2007; id142966 (Box 26, Item 3)
  - Hats (2), 2007; id142967 (Box 26, Item 4)
  - Water Bottle, 2007; id142968 (Box 26, Item 5)
  - 2nd Annual Houston Aeros Breast Cancer Awareness Hockey Puck, 2007; id142969 (Box 26, Item 6)
  - Lanyard and pin, 2007; id142970 (Box 26, Item 7)
  - T-shirts (9), 2008-2009; id142971 (Box 27, Item 1)
  - Pillowcase, 2008; id142972 (Box 27, Item 2)
  - Hat, 2008; id142973 (Box 27, Item 3)
  - Lanyards and pins (5), 2008-2010; id142974 (Box 27, Item 4)
  - Ink Pen, 2008; id142975 (Box 27, Item 5)
  - Chevron Toy Car “Spirit”, 2008; id142976 (Box 27, Item 6)
  - Souvenir bag, 2009; id142977 (Box 27, Item 7)
  - 4th Annual Houston Aeros Breast Cancer Awareness Hockey Puck, 2010; id142978 (Box 27, Item 8)
  - T-shirts (16), undated; id142979 (Box 28, Item 1)
  - T-shirts (9), undated; id142980 (Box 29, Item 1)
  - Shorts, undated; id142981 (Box 29, Item 2)
  - Hats (7), undated; id142982 (Box 29, Item 3)
  - Raincoat, undated; id142983 (Box 29, Item 4)
  - Fanny pack, undated; id142984 (Box 29, Item 5)
  - Canvas Bags (7), undated; id142985 (Box 30, Item 1)
  - Bedazzled Shoe, undated; id142986 (Box 30, Item 2)
  - Spaw Maxwell hard hat, undated; id142987 (Box 30, Item 3)
  - Chevron Cars “Hope”, undated; id142988 (Box 30, Item 4)
  - Water bottle, undated; id142989 (Box 30, Item 5)
  - Water bottle, undated; id142990 (Box 30, Item 6)
  - Stickers, name tags, other printed materials (11), undated; id142991 (Ovs box 31, Item 1)
  - Pins, 2008-2010 (11), undated; id142992 (Ovs box 31, Item 2)
  - Lip balm, undated; id142993 (Ovs box 31, Item 3)
  - “I am the Cure” Sign, undated; id142994 (Ovs box 31, Item 4)
  - Lanyards and medals (6), undated; id142995 (Ovs box 31, Item 5)
  - Ribbon and shoe strings (3), undated; id142996 (Ovs box 31, Item 6)
  - Arm bands and bracelets (6), undated; id142997 (Ovs box 31, Item 7)
  - Handkerchief and towel (3), undated; id142998 (Ovs box 31, Item 8)
  - Faux Pearl Necklace, undated; id142999 (Ovs box 31, Item 9)
  - “Reaching for the Cure” Coaster, undated; id143000 (Ovs box 31, Item 10)
  - Antenna Topper, undated; id143001 (Ovs box 31, Item 11)
  - Posters (English and Spanish), undated; id143002 (Ovs box 32, Item 1)
  - Posters (English and Spanish), undated; id143003 (Ovs box 32, Item 2)
  - Name banners (9), undated; id143004 (Ovs box 32, Item 3)
  - Komen banner, undated; id143005 (Ovs box 32, Item 4)
  - Komen Binder, undated; id143006 (Ovs box 32, Item 5)
  - Mobile Mammography Prints (2), undated; id143007 (Ovs box 32, Item 6)
  - Commemorative Bag, undated; id143008 (Ovs box 32, Item 7)
- Mulitmedia, id74712
  - Photographs, id143009
    - Harris County Hospital District, undated; id143016 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Race, undated; id143017 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Unknown Event, undated; id143018 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Various, undated; id143019 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Race Photographs (3), undated; id143020 (Ovs box 32, Item 14)
    - Race for the Cure Photo Album, 1995-1996; id143021 (Box 33, Item 1)
    - Race for the Cure Photo Album, 1997; id143022 (Box 33, Item 2)
    - Survivor Party/Membership Reception Photo Album, 1997; id143023 (Box 33, Item 3)
    - VIP Party/Membership Reception, 1998; id143024 (Box 33, Item 4)
    - Race for the Cure Photo Album, 1999; id143025 (Box 34, Item 1)
    - Sponsor Party Photo Album, 1999; id143026 (Box 34, Item 2)
    - Photo Album, undated; id143027 (Box 34, Item 3)
  - Audio, id143010
    - Race 1999, id143029 (Ovs box 35, Item 1)
    - “This Week in Houston w/ TJ Callahan”, 1999; id143030 (Ovs box 35, Item 2)
    - Remember PSA, undated; id143031 (Ovs box 35, Item 3)
    - 93.7 Radio Interview, undated; id143032 (Ovs box 35, Item 4)
  - Video, id143011
    - Race (2), 1997; id143034 (Ovs box 35, Item 5)
    - Race (2), 1997; id143035 (Ovs box 35, Item 6)
    - Race PSAs, 1998; id143036 (Ovs box 35, Item 7)
    - Race Television Segments, 1999; id143037 (Ovs box 35, Item 8)
    - Race, 2000; id143038 (Ovs box 35, Item 9)
    - Race, 2000; id143039 (Ovs box 35, Item 10)
    - Fox 4 News Fort Worth Race, 2001; id143040 (Ovs box 35, Item 11)
    - Race, undated; id143041 (Ovs box 35, Item 12)
    - Race, undated; id143042 (Ovs box 35, Item 13)
    - Race, undated; id143043 (Ovs box 35, Item 14)
    - Race, undated; id143044 (Ovs box 35, Item 15)
    - Remember PSA, 1999; id143045 (Ovs box 35, Item 16)
    - “Be a Survivor”, undated; id143046 (Ovs box 35, Item 17)
    - Affiliate Conference-Corporate Partner Presentations, 2003; id143047 (Ovs box 35, Item 18)
    - Affiliate Conference-Corporate Partner Presentations, 2005; id143048 (Ovs box 35, Item 19)
    - Healing and Preventing Domestic Violence, undated; id143049 (Ovs box 35, Item 20)